Guide to the Carolyn Caddes papers and photographs, circa 1980-2015
Stanford University Libraries.
- Subseries 3: Portraits of Success: Administrative Files (Acc # 1989- 175)
  - Portraits of Success: newspaper clippings, 1985- 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of West Magazine from San Jose Mercury News September 21, 1986 with article entitled “Do You Know Me? Face- to- face with Silicon Valley pioneers”. Another West magazine entitled “The 100 Most Powerful People in Silicon Valley” from June 7, 1987 is also included as well as a clipping from Business Week November 25, 1985.
  - Portraits of Success: newspaper clippings, 1986- 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of a Times Tribune article on Portraits of Silicon Valley Pioneers exhibit at Green Library at Stanford. November 8, 1986. Also included are articles about Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak, and other Silicon Valley pioneers.
  - Portraits of Success: newspaper clippings, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of the November issue of Bay Area Computer Currents.
  - Portraits of Success: newsapaper clippings, 1986- 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of clippings about Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: newspaper clippings, 1986- 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Portraits of Success: newspaper clippings, 1985- 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Portraits of Success: papers and photographs, 1984- 1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of paperwork and photography relating to Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: Texas visit, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of information pertaining to Caddes' visit to Texas to speak about her book.
  - Preface, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of drafts of the book's preface.
  - Printing information, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of printing information about Portraits of Success.
  - Profiles, 1982- 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of articles and clippings about some of the key people featured in the book.
  - Publishing, 1981- 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of notes and clippings pertaining to publishing Portraits of Success.
  - Query: requests for agents and help (Box 18, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of letters to publishers, rejections and drafts of proposals to get Portraits of Success published.
  - Questionnaires, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of notes and drafts of questionnaires sent to the book's subjects before their portrait sessions.
  - Release forms, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of drafts and copies of release forms which the book subjects signed.
  - S.Valley plan and letters, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of plans for the book and letters Caddes wrote for people she wanted to photograph for the book.
  - Sample biographies, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of sample biographies of some of the book subjects.
  - Schares, Gail, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of notes and correspondence.
  - Science musuem, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of clippings, notes and research on the opening of a science musuem in Silicon Valley.
  - Signatures, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of signatures and forms from the book's subjects.
  - Jim Stockton, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of notes, correspondence, clippings and brochures on designing the book.
  - Tioga Publishing, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of correspondence, notes and information about Tioga Publishing.
  - T.V. interaction with John Krump, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Writer, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    The materials consist of correspondence and notes concerning Caddes' search for a writer to help with the book.
  - Wolfe, Tom, 1981- 1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    The materials consist of correspondence, clippings and notes.
- Subseries 4: Portraits of Success: Photographs (Acc # 1989-175)
  The materials consist of a mix of duplicate photographs of subjects from the book, additional images from the portrait session and other subjects who were not included in the final product.
  - Adams, Jim, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Amdahl, Gene, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Atanasoff, Jim, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bardeen, Jack, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Breiner, Sheldon, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Bushnell, Nolan, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Chodorow, Marvin, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Cook, Paul, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Corrigan, Will, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Thomas, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Dennis, Reid, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Draper, William, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Dwight, Herbert, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Eckert, Presper, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Engelbart, Douglas, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fairchild Eight, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Feigenbaum, Edward, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Ferrey, Ed, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Friedenrich, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Gibbons, James, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Ginsburg, Charles, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Ginzton, Edward, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Grove, Andy, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Halperin, Robert, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Hambrecht, William, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Haughton, Kenneth, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Hewlett, William, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Hoerni, Jean, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Hoff, Marcian "Ted", undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Hogan, Lester, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Jobs, Steve, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Johnson, Franklin "Pitch", undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Johnson, H. Richard, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Kay, Alan, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Kays, William, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Kelley, Tom, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Kleiner, Eugene, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Knuth, Donald, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Kurtzig, Sandra, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Maxfield, Robert, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - McCarthy, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - McMurtry, Burton, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Meindl, James, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Melchor, Jack, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mineta, Norman, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous photocopies, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous photocopies, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Moore, Gordon, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Noyce, Robert, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Osborne, Adam, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - McKenna, Regis, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Oshman, M. Kenneth, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Packard, David, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Pake, George, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Perkins, Thomas (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Perry, William, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Quate, Cal, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Robertson, Sanford, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Rock, Arthur, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Root, Eugene, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sanders, Jerry, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Schawlow, Arthur, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Shockley, William, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Shugart, Alan, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Siegman, Anthony, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Silicon Valley buildings, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Sonsini, Larry, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Sporck, Charles, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Swanson, Robert, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Terman, Frederick, undatde (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Treybig, James G., undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Watkins, Dean, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Whinnery, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Wilson, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Wozniak, Steve, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Yelverton, Jack, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Young, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Zaffaroni, Alex, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Zschau, Ed, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Duplicate photographs: Subjects A- D (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Duplicate photographs: Subjects E- H (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Duplicate photographs: Subjects J- K (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Duplicate photographs: Subjects M- O (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Duplicate photographs: Subjects P-S (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate photographs: Subjects T-Z (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Subseries 5: Portraits of Success: Oversized newspaper clippings (Acc # 1989- 175) (Box 21)
- Subseries 6: Portraits of Success: Oversized photographs (Acc # 1989- 175) (Box 22)
  - Writing drafts (Box 22, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of drafts and editors' notes for Portraits of Success.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Photograph draft (Box 22, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of a draft of the book with photographs only.
  - Text and photograph draft (Box 22, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of a draft of the book with text and photographs.
  - Additional book files (Box 22, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of drafts of the introduction, glossary and bibliography.
  - Computers chapter draft (Box 22, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of drafts of computer chapter of Portraits of Success.
  - Electronics technology chapter draft (Box 22, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of drafts of the electronics technology chapter of Portraits of Sucess.
  - Semiconductors chapter draft (Box 22, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of a draft of the semiconductor chapter of Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of portrait prints.
  - Portraits (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Portraits (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Oversized Portraits (Box 22, Folder 12)
    The materials consist of oversized portrait prints.
  - Support chapter draft (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Farichild semiconductor (Box 22, Folder 14)
    The materials consist of portraits of Fairchild semiconductor.
- Series 2: Nikkei Magazine (Acc # 2003- 274)
  The materials consist of research, correspondence, clippings and notes for an article written by Caddes for Nikkei Magazine, a Japanese business publication.
  - Subseries 1: Administrative files
    - Business cards, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
      The materials consist of business cards of individuals from EDS (Electronic Data Systems), Netscape, Echelon, the National Women’s Hall of Fame and Technology Venture Investors. Also a sheet of subjects and companies appearing in “Silicon Valley Pioneers-Now” or “The Most Important People in Silicon Valley”.
    - Corporate brochures, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Consultants, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      The materials consist of spreadsheet of addresses, emails and phone numbers of subjects and their assistants. Also included are suggestions for 1995 Nikkei series and correspondence about those subjects.
    - Japan information, 1995- 1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of correspondence, notes, clippings and adminstrative information.
    - Magazines, 1995- 1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      The materials consist of issues of Nikkei Magazine from 1995 and 1997.
    - Magazines, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      The materials consist of issues of Nikkei Business Magazine from 1999.
    - Mayumi and airport, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      The materials consist of correspondence with Mayumi of Nikkei Magazine and prints of Southwest gate at San Jose airport.
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
      The materials consist of Japanese newspaper clippings.
    - Nikkei news, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      The materials consist of correspondence and research for Nikkei magazine articles.
    - Norri Kageki, 1996- 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      The materials consist of correspondence, research, invoices and writing in collaborate with Nikkei writer, Norri Kageki.
    - Photo costs, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      The materials consist of information from Custom Color Lab and notes.
    - Prints and negatives (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Research (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Signatures, 1995- 1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Airlines Gate, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      The materials consist of prints and negatives of Southwest Airlines gate at San Jose Airport.
    - Tests, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of negatives and prints of color tests.
  - Subseries 2: Research and photographs
    - Andersen, Marc, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
      The materials consist of prints and negatives of Marc Andersen of Netscape.
    - Aymar, Mike, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels for Mike Aymar, Intel Corporation.
    - Barrett, Craig, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      The materials consist of correspondence, prints, clippings, notes and labels concerning Craig Barrett of Intel Corporation.
    - Bartz, Carol, 1995- 1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of correspondence, research and newspaper clippings concerning Autodesk and the CEO during the mid 1990s, Carol Bartz.
    - Carter, Dennis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      The materials consist of prints, negatives and lables of Dennis Carter of Intel Corporation.
    - Clark, James, 1995- 1996 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      The materials consist of correspondence, research and newspaper clippings of James Clark, CEO of Netscape. Also included are transparencies from his portrait session with Caddes and a narrative of their interaction.
    - Coleman, Debie, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Cook, Paul, 1995- 1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      The materials consist of information about Scott D. Cook, Co-founder and chairman of Intuit, Inc which developed Quicken. Also included are Caddes’ notes on their conversation, research on the company and transparencies of his portraits.
    - Crawford, John, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels of John Crawford of Intel Corporation.
    - Doerr, John, 1996- 2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      The materials consist of information pertaining to John Doerr, one of the partners of the venture capitalist firm Kleiner Perkins Caufield and Byers. This folder includes research on the company, a first draft of Caddes’ interview with him and correspondence with Doerr and his family.
    - Drucker, Peter, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      The materials consist of research and correspondence.
    - Dulong, Carole, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      The materials consist of correspondence, prints and negatives.
    - Ellison, Larry, 1995- 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      The materials consist of negatives, newspaper clippings, interview questions and company research concerning Larry Ellison, CEO of Oracle.
    - Gates, Bill, 1996- 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      The materials consist of correspondence with Bill Gates, CEO of Microsoft. Includes company research, articles on Gates’s new home in Seattle, transparencies from portrait session and a copy of Time magazine from September 1996.
    - Gelsinger, Pat, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels for Pat Gelsinger of Intel Corporation.
    - Gill, Frank, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels for Frank Gill of Intel Corporation.
    - Grove, Andy, 1996- 1998 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of correspondence with Andy Grove, CEO of Intel. This folder also contains newspaper clippings and articles about his battle with prostate cancer. Also included is company information and brochures from Intel’s museum.
    - Hewlett Packard, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      The materials consist of a copy of Measure, HP’s magazine as well as their newsletter, Watt’s Current.
    - Intel, 1991- 1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Intel invoices, 1997- 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      The materials consist of invoices and financial information for Caddes' portrait sessions with Intel employees.
    - Intel photo album, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
      The materials consist of a photo album of Intel employees' portraits.
    - Intel publications, 1989- 1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      The materials consist of Intel's publications including annual reports, museum brochures and Intel This Week.
    - Jobs, Steve: clippings, 1991- 1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      The materials consist of newspaper clippings relating to Steve Jobs. Many of these clippings are about Jobs' new venture at the time, Pixar and its first feature film Toy Story which premiered in 1995.
    - Jobs, Steve: correspondence, 1996- 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      The materials consist of correspondence setting up Jobs' portrait session and about the sale of the portrait of Robert Noyce to Jobs.
    - Jobs, Steve: photography files, 1996- 1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of slides, correspondence, invoices and negatives.
    - Konar, Ellen, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels for Ellen Konar.
    - Kurtzig, Sandra, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      The materials consist of notes, correspondence and negatives of Sandra Kurtzig.
    - McCracken, Ed, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      The materials consist of correspondence, biography, notes, clippings and slides of Edward McCracken.
    - McMurtry, Burton, 1995- 1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      The materials consist of slides, correspondence, writing and research on Burton McMurtry.
    - Moore, Gordon, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      The materials consist of negatives, labels, prints and correspondence.
    - Morgan, Becky and Jim, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      The materials consist of correspondence, notes, negatives and prints.
    - Morgridge, John, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      The materials consist of writing, correspondence, company research and slides.
    - Oshman, Kenneth, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      The materials consist of correspondence, slides and company information.
    - Otellini, Paul, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels of Paul Otellini
    - Parker, Gerry, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      The materials consist of negatives and labels.
    - Rosen, Ben, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      The materials consist of correspondence and writing.
    - Sanders, Jerry, 1994- 1996 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      The materials consist of slides, notes, correspondence, writing and company research.
    - Silicon Valley Rising Star, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      The materials consist of prints and negatives of Linus Torvalds and SSteve Jurvetson, subjects in the Silicon Valley Rising Star series.
    - Sonsini, Larry, 1995- 1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      The materials consist of slides, correspondence, writing and labels.
    - Sun Microsystems, 1995- 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      The materials consist of clippings, prints, company information and research.
    - Toffler, Alvin, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of slides, notes and correspondence.
    - Treybig, James, 1994- 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      The materials consist of annual reports, correspondence, slides and research.
    - Whittier, Ron, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      The materials consist of prints, negatives and labels.
    - Wozniak, Steve, 1995- 1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      The materials consist of correspondence, clippings, fundraiser programs and notes.
    - Wozniak, Steve: photography files, 1995- 1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      The materials consist of prints, negatives, slides and correspondence.
    - Young, John, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      The materials consist of correspondence, clippings, notes and slides.
    - Yu, Albert, 1996- 1997 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      The materials consist of slides, negatives, prints, notes and correspondence.
  - Subseries 3: Slides
    - Alvares, Kenneth, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Apple Computers, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Breiner, Sheldon, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Chandrasekhor, K.B., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Clark, James, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Cook, Scott, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Dennis, Reid, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Dreskin, Andrew, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Drucker, Peter, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Ellison, Larry, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - First Fairchild Headquarters, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Gates, Bill, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Gerzburg, Levy, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Grove, Andy, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Harada, Eikoh, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Hewlett, William, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Hewlett Packard executives (Box 29, Folder 17)
      The materials consist of slides of Ann Livermore, Susie Wee, Bob Wayman, Gene Baker and the Cool Town Demo Room.
    - Hewlett Packard sites, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Jobs, Steve, 1995- 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Robin, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Kaplan, Jerry, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Kurtzig, Sandra, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Marquardt, David, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - McCracken, Ed, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - McMurtry, Burton, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - McNealy, Scott, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous slides (Folder 1 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Miscelleaneous slides (Folder 2 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Microsoft buildings, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Moore, Gordon, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Morgridge, John, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Moritz, Michael, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Oshman, Kenneth, 1995- 1996 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Pankin, Jon, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Park, The, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Parker, George, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Peters, Tom, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Raduchel, William, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Rock, Art, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Rosen, Ben, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Rosen, Harold, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sanders, Jerry, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Saunders, Anne, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Schmidt, Eric, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Sonsini, Larry, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Sun Microsystems, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Sun Microsystems building, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ticket web, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Toffler, Alvin, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Treybig, James, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - The Gates Computer Science Building, Stanford University, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Wozniak, Margaret, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Wozniak, Steve, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Wythes, Paul, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Young, John, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Slide holders and microcassettes, 1995- 1996 (Box 32)
      The materials consist of slide holders for Peter Drucker. Microcasettes of John Morgridge, Jerry Sanders, Paul Cook, Andy Grove, John Doerr, Sandra Kurtzig, Larry Ellison, Burton McMurtry, Steve Wozniak, John Young, Kenneth Oshman, Ed McCracken, James Clark, James Treybig and Larry Sonsini.
- Series 3: California Winemakers (Acc # 2004- 091), 1982- 1993
  The materials consist of photographs, research and correspondence from Caddes' follow up project to Portraits of Success. She wanted to complete another Portraits of Success book focused on California wine makers. She traveled around Napa Valley between 1992 and 1993 and interviewed some of the most influential wine makers at the time. The book was never published.
  - Adams, Leon, 1990- 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of correspondence between Carolyn Caddes and Leon Adams, a copy of California Wine Industry Oral History Project. This section is entitled “Leon Adams: California Wine Industry Affairs: Recollections and Opinions”. Also included are negatives, prints and copies from the portait session.
  - Amerine, Maynard, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)